<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1970s on Noah Mazer</title>
    <link>https://noahmazer.com/tags/1970s/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1970s on Noah Mazer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://noahmazer.com/tags/1970s/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eduardo Galeano - On Roque Dalton </title>
      <link>https://noahmazer.com/blog/sobre-roque-dalton/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noahmazer.com/blog/sobre-roque-dalton/</guid>
      <description>[Sobre Roque Dalton]
Roque Dalton makes the stones laugh. He was the least solemn of all of us, and he pulled Death’s leg too. So I won’t go writing, now, a tear-dampened necrology in his memory.
But I can’t refrain from saying that I was disgusted by the press’s silence, and I can’t refrain from noting the double pain that death provokes when you learn about it so late. The teletypes of the big international agencies didn’t vibrate to report on the murder of the poet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luis Rogelio Nogueras - Obituary </title>
      <link>https://noahmazer.com/blog/luis-rogelio-nogueras-obituario/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noahmazer.com/blog/luis-rogelio-nogueras-obituario/</guid>
      <description>[Obituario]
We were a mask, in English pants, Parisian
vest, a coat from the United States, and a Spanish
bullfighter&amp;rsquo;s hat.
MARTÍ
They buried him in the heart of a pine forest
and still
the pinewood coffin was imported from Ohio
they buried him by an iron mine and still
the nails of his coffin and the iron of the shovel were imported from Pittsburg;
they buried him next to the world’s best sheep pasture and still</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roque Dalton - Poem XVI </title>
      <link>https://noahmazer.com/blog/roque-dalton-poema-xvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noahmazer.com/blog/roque-dalton-poema-xvi/</guid>
      <description>[Poema XVI]
The laws are made
for the poor to follow. The laws are made by the rich to give a little order to exploitation. The poor are the only followers of the laws of history.
When the poor make the laws the rich will be no more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>